<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GP on Ghenadie Pusca</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in GP on Ghenadie Pusca</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2020, Ghenadie Pusca; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Functions in Swift</title>
      <link>/blog/functions_in_swift/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/functions_in_swift/</guid>
      <description>Swift is a multi-paradigm language, in light terms meaning you can do both Object Oriented Programming and Functional Programming. Even though it can do both, and even at the same time, in same program, we usually focus most of our attention and care to the Object Oriented part, and ignoring, leaving or take it as granted at functions can offer. And functions have to offer a lot. In this post we&amp;rsquo;ll take a high level look what functions can do, beyond theyre normal usage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If expression in Swift [SICP 1]</title>
      <link>/blog/if_expressions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/if_expressions/</guid>
      <description>This blogpost is a part of going through the SICP book, you can get a free copy from:
https://web.mit.edu/alexmv/6.037/sicp.pdf
A while ago, I’ve heard about functional programming. Being in the pursuit of improving my skills as a programmer, all of the functional methodologies and rules, seem to be of a great value. Thus, I embark in a journey of learning functional programming principles, by trying to implement all of them in Swift programming language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Hugo</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is the world’s fastest framework for building websites. It is written in Go.
It makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
 https://github.com/russross/blackfriday https://github.com/alecthomas/chroma https://github.com/muesli/smartcrop https://github.com/spf13/cobra https://github.com/spf13/viper  Learn more and contribute on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>